- Starting compressions.
- Let me get it attached.
- One, two, three. Breathe.
- Stand by and...
- Yeah, we're good.
One, two, three. Breathe.
Come on, baby. Come on.
Still nothing.
Come on.
Will she be okay?
Who's going to tell him
to brush his teeth
before breakfast now?
Or go to Costco
to buy the right Nivea?
I'm sorry.
I know there's thousands
of parents
every year
who go through this.
I can do this.
I'm strong.
I hope.
Thank you for sharing, Cheryl.
This can be so challenging.
Especially for parents like us
who spend more time
with their children than most.
But if I remember correctly,
there's actually
one other parent here
going through the same thing.
Diane?
How do you feel?
How do I feel about...
Chloe's going to college
in a few months.
How do you feel?
Good.